Billy Byers Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Full Scores (Box 1-35)
  - Boston Pops
    - What a fool believes: May 1, 1980, Reduced and bound photocopy. (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Brown Rice
    - Berknee guitar player: MGM Records (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Drowsy eyes: MGM Records (Box-folder 5/7)
    - We can see the sun: MGM Records (Box-folder 5/8)
    - White dove (Box-folder 5/9)
  - Browne, Leslie
    - Ballet (Box-folder 5/10)
  - Bull frog, Composed and arranged by Byers. (Box-folder 5/11)
  - Burnett, Carol see also Steve and Eydie
    - Suppertime: Berlin show/Smith-Hemion/live tv 1978 (Box-folder 5/12)
  - Burns, George see Ann-Margret
  - Bushkin, Joe
    - After today: Nov. 30, 1967 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Beautiful things (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Cross road (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Dr. Doolittle (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Fabulous places (Box-folder 5/17)
    - I think I like you (Box-folder 5/18)
    - My friend the Doctor (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Talk to the animals (Box-folder 5/20)
    - Thoroughly modern Millie (Box-folder 5/21)
    - The vegetarian (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Walking happy (Box-folder 5/23)
    - When I look in your eyes (Box-folder 5/24)
  - Butler, Jerry see The Music Scene
  - Byner, John
    - J.B. bows (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Long and winding road combo, Includes "Can’t smile without you." (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Maybe this time, For John McCook. (Box-folder 5/27)
    - The way we were (Box-folder 5/28)
  - Calucci’s Dept.: tv film see also Hamlisch, Marvin
    - Opening I - short version: Aug. 30, 1973 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Opening I - long version (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Opening II short version: live tv Aug. 30, 1973 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Opening II long version (Box-folder 5/29)
    - End crawl - long and short (Box-folder 5/29)
    - End crawl II - short and long (Box-folder 5/29)
  - Can we get together again (Box-folder 5/30)
  - Can’t smile without you (Box-folder 5/31)
  - Cardinal, Vin
    - All in all (Box-folder 6/1)
    - Hitchcock railway (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Let the water run down (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Why can’t I touch you? (Box-folder 6/4)
  - Carpenters see also ABC 25th anniversary
    - Spaceships transposing: vaudeville 1978 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Thank you: vaudeville 1978 Thank you-bows (Box-folder 6/6)
  - Carroll, Diahann see also Rodgers/Hart tv special
    - As time goes by: Joe Guercio prop. (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Bridge over troubled water: May 17, 1971 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Fire and rain: NBC Dean Martin Show (Box-folder 6/9)
    - Good lovin’: May 18, 1971 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - I am...I said: May 15, 1971 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Love number: May 18, 1971, Includes "Help me make it through the night." (Box-folder 6/12)
    - This is your life: NBC Dean Martin Show Sept. 27, 1978 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - This minute: Star Wars [special], Smith-Hemion 1978 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - [What are you doing] the rest of your life: Diahann Carroll special NBC March 15, 1970 (Box-folder 6/15)
  - Carter, Mel
    - Enter laughing: Columbia Pictures Corp., Ambassador Hotel (Box-folder 6/16)
  - Cassidy, Jack see Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy
  - Cavett, Dick
    - Movies were movies: TV special, RCA 1976 (Box-folder 6/17)
  - Chaiken, Jules (prod.)
    - Here comes Virginia (Box-folder 6/18)
  - Chakiris, George
    - Something’s coming–opening (Box-folder 6/19)
  - Charmolesque (Box-folder 6/20)
  - Clark, Dick
    - Birdland: live TV 1978, For Buddy [Rich] and pal. (Box-folder 6/21)
  - Como, Perry
    - [Untitled], For John. (Box-folder 6/22)
  - Craver, Sonny see Basie, Count
  - Cronin, Kei
    - Alone in crowd (Box-folder 6/23)
    - Buffalo (Box-folder 6/24)
    - Soldier (Box-folder 6/25)
  - Crosby, Bing
    - Ac-cent-tchu-ate the positive, For Bing and Bette Midler. (Box-folder 6/26)
    - Christmas medley: TV special, 1975, Includes "Jingle bells;" "Sleighride;" "Toyland;" "Let it snow;" "Have yourself a merry little Christmas."; For Bing, Fred [Astaire] & FAA. (Box-folder 7/1)
    - Everything old is new again: TV special, 1977, Includes "Baby face;" "Toot toot tootsie;" "I’m looking over a four leaf clover." (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Everything old–chaser (Box-folder 7/2)
    - In the blue of the night: vaudeville 1976 In the blue of the night - underscore [In the] blue of [the] night closing (Box-folder 7/3)
    - It’s not where you start: Day Break Records, June 1973 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - Moonlight becomes you: TV special, 1977 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - Ol’ man river (Box-folder 7/6)
    - Opening-closing (Box-folder 7/7)
    - Tie a yellow ribbon: Day Break Records/MGM Fairfax (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Crosby, Harry
    - I won’t last a day without you: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Curtis, Anthony (prod.)
    - Player play on (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Tomorrow is a brand new day (Box-folder 7/11)
    - What makes a dance feel so good: July 26, 1966 (Box-folder 7/12)
  - Damone, Vic
    - If you are but a dream: RCA, Dec. 19, 1967 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - Nearness of you – Time was – As time goes by: TV (show 4), Includes manuscript and a printed copy. (Box-folder 7/14)
    - Watch what happens: RCA, Dec. 19, 1967 (Box-folder 7/15)
  - Dana, Bill see Martin Show, Tony
  - Dancing Machine
    - Transition #1 Transition #2 (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Davidson, John see Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
  - Davis, Charles
    - Finale: vaudeville 1978 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Opening: vaudeville 1978, Includes "I wanna make the world laugh." (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Davis, Jr., Sammy see also Steve and Eydie; Minnelli, Liza and Sammy Davis Jr.; Rodgers/Hart tv special; Stop the World I Want to Get Off
    - [Alexander’s ragtime band] Van Alexander’s Roseland band: Berlin show – Smith/Hemion – live TV, 1978 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - It’s a musical world: MGM discs, July 14, 1972 (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Dear friend – Will he like me – medley, Keyboard and vocal parts laid in; indicates for 3 Girls 3; arranged by Johnny Mandel. (Box-folder 7/21)
  - The Dells see The Music Scene
  - Denver, John
    - Pineapple rag: John Denver Show (Box-folder 7/22)
  - Diamond, Neil
    - Holly holly: Nov. 17, 1969 (Box-folder 7/23)
  - Dickey, Joe
    - Little boy lost, Paper stained. (Box-folder 7/24)
  - Didn't we?, Performer “K.” (Box-folder 7/25)
  - Diller, Phyllis
    - Fine and dandy - play off: The Phyllis Diller Show (Box-folder 8/1)
    - Love a lot part I (finale) new lead in: Phyllis Diller Show, Arranged by Luther Henderson. (Box-folder 8/2)
    - Magic time: The Phyllis Diller Show, Arranged by Luther Henderson. (Box-folder 8/3)
    - Mary zoo - play on - play off: The Phyllis Diller Show, Arranged by Luther Henderson. (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Eckstine, Billy
    - A day in the life of a fool: Roosevelt Hotel, Aug. 15, 1968 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - A day in the life of a fool (Box-folder 8/5)
    - Dedicated to you: PBS, With Sarah Vaughan. (Box-folder 8/6)
    - For once in my life: Motown, Dec. 25, 1965 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - If she walked into my life: Stax Records - T.T.G., Jan. 15, 1964 If she walked into my life: Jan. 24, 1974 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - I’ll never miss her till I think of her (Box-folder 8/9)
    - I’m so very happy: Joey Bishop ABC, Oct. 6, 1969 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - Maybe this time: Stax Records T.T.G. Jan. 15, 1973 Maybe this time, Jan. 24, 1974 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - Michelle - sketch: Motown Dec. 25, 1965 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - The need to be: vaudeville 1975 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - Once in a lifetime: MotownDec. 25 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Prelude to a kiss: Public broadcasting (Box-folder 8/15)
    - Remembering: Stax Records T.T.G. Dec. 15, 1974 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - The slender thread: Motown (Box-folder 8/17)
    - The very thought of you: Stax Records (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Yesterday: Motown Records Dec. 20, 1965 (Box-folder 8/19)
  - Eckstein, Lulita
    - Still: vaudeville 1979 (Box-folder 8/20)
  - Eden, Barbara
    - Love story: Barbara Eden/Telly Savalas TV special, 1976 (Box-folder 8/21)
  - Elliot, Cass aka Mama Cass
    - Broadway bar and grill, The: TV special 73 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - Cass’ golden oldies, Includes "Make your own kind of music;" "Dream a little dream of me;" "New world coming." (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Don’t call me Mama anymore: TV special #73 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - Extraordinary; Opening - extraordinary (Box-folder 8/25)
    - Hang up your hat Phil Feldman: special 73 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - I’m a tree: 73 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - Mama undescore + crawl (Box-folder 8/28)
    - Mama’s party (Box-folder 8/29)
    - [Miscellaneous TV cues]: special 73 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - Orange color sky: March 15, 1972; You can’t kill rock and roll (Box-folder 8/31)
    - Those were the days: TV special Aug. 30, 1973 (Box-folder 8/32)
    - Tuesday, Tuesday: TV special 73 (Box-folder 8/33)
    - Up to now: special #73 (Box-folder 8/34)
  - Everly Brothers see Sinatra, Nancy
  - Falana, Lola see also Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
    - Academy 71 medley: May 9, 1971, Includes "We’ve only just begun;" "Love story;" "Till love touches your life."; Printed score. (Box-folder 9/1)
    - The best is yet to come (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Gonna make you love me: May 9, 1971 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - [I gotta] right to sing the blues (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Imagination: May 9, 1971 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - In the city (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Never can say good-bye: May 2, 1971 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - She’s a lady: May 9, 1971 She’s a lady II: May 10, 1971 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - Sweet Lord - Happy day: May 2, 1971 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - The twelfth of never (Box-folder 9/10)
    - What a difference a day makes: May 9, 1971 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - What about today (Box-folder 9/12)
  - The Farmer’s Daughter
    - Orange colored sky: MGM, March 15, 1972 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Ford Special
    - May the good Lord bless [and] keep you: NBC#2 Sept. 18, 1971 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Take your girlie to the movies (closing): NBC Sept. 18, 1971 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Four Tops
    - Wives and lovers: Motown - Jerry Long March 12, 1965 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Franchi, Sergio
    - George M. Cohan medley: Vaudeville ‘75, Includes "Give my regards to Broadway;" "Mary’s a grand old name;" "I’m a Yankee-doodle dandy;" "You’re a grand old flag." (Box-folder 9/17)
    - It was a good time: March 18, 1974 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Top hat (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Tradition (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Gaynor, Mitzi
    - Auto bahn on (Box-folder 9/21)
    - Bump no fat woman: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - Can we get together again: live TV 77 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - The charleston (Box-folder 9/24)
    - The charleston [bows] (Box-folder 9/25)
    - Cleaning stings (Box-folder 9/26)
    - Cold opening: TV special 1977 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - Deep purple: TV (Live)1977 (Box-folder 9/28)
    - Don’t you feel my leg (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Feudin’ and fightin’: Mitzi Gaynor Show, 1976, For Scott & David; condensed vocal score. (Box-folder 10/2)
    - Foto montage (Box-folder 10/3)
    - [It] might as well be [spring] on [It] might as well be [spring] off (Box-folder 10/4)
    - Let’s do it verse Let’s do it 6-x Let’s do it bridge Let’s do it coda (Box-folder 10/5)
    - Limehouse blues: special (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Love will find a way, Lead sheet with orchestral annotations. (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Melting pot on Melting pot I: 1976, Includes "America;" "Brotherhood of man." (Box-folder 10/7)
    - Melting pot part II, Includes "My wild Irish rose;" "Danny boy;" "Tzena, Tzena, Tzena;" "I’ve got a lovely bunch of cocoanuts;" "My melody of love;" "Golden earrings;" "Pass that peace pipe." (Box-folder 10/8)
    - Melting pot III: 1976, Includes "Winchester Cathedral;" "I’ve got a lovely bunch of cocoanuts." (Box-folder 10/9)
    - [Melting pot] m.p. IV, Includes "Wien;" "O du Lieber Augustin." (Box-folder 10/10)
    - [Melting pot] m.p. V, Includes "My wild Irish rose;" "Danny boy;" "It’s the same old shillelagh." (Box-folder 10/11)
    - Melting pot VI, Includes "Golden earrings;" "Moja dro ga jacie kocham;" "My melody of love." (Box-folder 10/12)
    - Melting pot #2: 1976, Includes "Wey Marie;" "Oh mama;" "Darling, je vous aime beacoup;" "Ah cherie;" "Frère Jacques;" "Ta-ra-ra Boom-de-ay;" "Comin’ thru the rye;" "The Campbells are coming;" "Shalom;" "Hava nagila;" "Tzena, Tzena, Tzena." (Box-folder 10/13)
    - Nursery rhyme: vaudeville 1976 Nursery [rhyme] part II: vaudeville 1976 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - Overture 76 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - Scoreboard part III: TV special (Box-folder 10/16)
    - Some people: June 1, 1974 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - South Pacific entracte - S.P. medley, Dec. 2, 199112/2/91, Includes "A cockeyed optimist;" "You’ve got to be carefully taught." (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Spring cleaning play on Spring cleaning play off (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Sugar blues - Fifth of Beethoven (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Symphony #5: L. van Beethoven (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Takin’ care of business: 1976, For Scott & David; condensed vocal score. (Box-folder 10/22)
    - The tango: TV 76 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - Them there eyes: special (Box-folder 10/24)
    - [Twelfth] 12th Street intro (Box-folder 10/25)
    - We who are about to diet: live TV 77 [We who are about to] diet play on (Box-folder 10/26)
    - [When you’re] smiling/[I want to be] happy: vaudeville 76 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - Glow, Bernie
    - Glow’s worms: 1979, Arrangement of "Glow worm;" includes lead sheet. (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Gorme, Eydie see Steve and Edydie
  - Goulet, Robert/Carol Lawrence
    - B & C overture 70: June 14, 1970 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Better all the time: June 12, 1970 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - Love story: A.M. June 15, 1970, Includes fixes. (Box-folder 11/4)
    - The town that won’t sleep (Box-folder 11/5)
  - Graham, Virginia
    - Everybody’s talking: KAJ-TV (Box-folder 11/6)
  - Grand entrance: #2a (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Grey, Joel see also Minnelli, Liza
    - Billy Rose medley, Includes: "Great day;" "Paper moon;" "More than you know;" "Don’t bring Lulu;" "Me and my shadow;" "Back in your own back yard." (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Cabaret, including Wilkommen; Money, money Cabaret fanfare Cabaret fix (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Final bows Final bows, new (Box-folder 11/10)
    - One of a kind (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Roumania (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Grayson, Kathryn see Keel, Howard and [Kathryn] Grayson
  - Greco, Buddy
    - My favorite things: Oct. 22, 1965 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - When I’m not near the one I love: Oct. 24, 1965 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - Hadjidakis, Manos
    - Les Athletes: Mercury Records, May 26, 1965, A photocopy. (Box-folder 11/15)
    - The boy is very sensual: Mercury Records, May 21, 1965 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - La Contesse Esterhazy: Mercury Records, May 19, 1965, A photocopy. (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Song for my mother: Mercury Records, May 29, 1965, A photocopy. (Box-folder 11/18)
    - Les Wages sont commencer: Mercury Records, May 20, 1964, Two copies; photocopy. (Box-folder 11/19)
    - Waltz with my shadow: Mercury Records, May 24, 1965, A photocopy. (Box-folder 11/20)
    - Parts (Box-folder 33/6-7)
  - Hamill, Dorothy see also Kelly, Gene
    - B.G. #1: TV, 1976 (Box-folder 11/21)
    - Opening: Hemion + Smith prod. TV, 1976, For Gene Kelly and choir. Includes "Somewhere over the rainbow;" "I’m always chasing rainbows." (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Hamlisch, Marvin, Items with “m-#'s” probably for Calucci’s Dept.
    - Allison: m-22 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - Dee Elliot main theme: m-11 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Eldreb laughs: m-12 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - Heliotrope bouquet: MCA Records (Box-folder 12/4)
    - I love a piano: MCA stompers (Box-folder 12/5)
    - The man that got away: Danny Thomas special (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Newley-Hamlisch overture: vaudeville 1977 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - Picks her up: m-14/21 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - Playin’ with aim: m-42 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - Ragtime nightingale: MCA discs (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Rialto ripples: MCA Records (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Stop time rag (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Thanks for giving her a list: m-23 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Hanna-Barbera
    - Dance machine transition #3 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Honey’s telephone, For Honey. (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Opening, #1 + #1a Opening, new, For Betty. (Box-folder 12/16)
    - Sing sing sing: Hanna-Barbera happy hour, For Gary and Betty. (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Happy Birthday Las Vegas ‘77
    - Bake a cake (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Happy birthday Las Vegas opening: live T.V. (Box-folder 12/19)
    - Happy birthday Las Vegas underscore #1; Happy birthday Las Vegas underscore #2, Arranged by Nan Schwartz. (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Happy birthday Las Vegas underscore #3 (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Happy birthday Las Vegas underscore #4, Arranged by Nan Schwartz. (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Happy birthday Las Vegas underscore #5 (Box-folder 12/20)
    - Hello Dolly, finale, For Tony. (Box-folder 12/21)
    - Higher and higher (your love keeps lifting me): live TV 77, For John Davidson. (Box-folder 12/22)
    - How great Thou art, For Dionne Warwick. (Box-folder 12/23)
    - Luck be a lady; Luck be a lady - house band, For Doc [Severinson]. (Box-folder 12/24)
    - Midnight at the oasis, For Lola Falana. (Box-folder 12/25)
    - Vegas parade: live tv 77 (Box-folder 12/26)
    - Vegas parade school band (Box-folder 12/27)
    - Well did you ever [sic], For Wayne Newton. (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Hartman, David
    - Her face: vaudeville (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Here’s that rainy day: vaudeville arrangement, Nov. 1, 1969 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Little green apples: vaudeville arrangement, Nov. 1, 1969 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - On a wonderful day like today: vaudeville, Nov. 11, 1969 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - They call the wind Maria: vaudeville arrangement, Oct. 25, 1969 They call the wind Maria - insert (Box-folder 13/5)
    - This guy’s in love with you: vaudeville arrangement (Box-folder 13/6)
    - This is all I ask: vaudeville arrangement, Jan. 24, 1970 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Hawn, Goldie see also Minnell, Liza and Goldie Hawn
    - Thirties opening: 73, Includes "A fine romance;" "Let’s call the whole thing off;" "Where or when;" "They can’t take that away from me;" "With plenty of money and you;" "We’re in the money;" "Temptation;" "Down in the depths;" "Forty-second Street;" "Lullaby of Broadway." (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Thirties bows: 73 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Heatherton, Joey
    - Falling ballad medley: vaudeville 79, Includes "They say it’s wonderful;" "When I fall in love." (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Falling medley - insert (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Finale ‘75 new ending: vaudeville (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Helmsley & Weeks
    - Doo dee doo: 1975 vaudeville (Box-folder 13/11)
    - For the rest of my life: ‘75 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Hello Dolly insert, Includes "Hello Dolly;" "Don’t rain on my parade." (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Reach out and touch (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Reachin’ for the stars (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Hines, Mimi
    - Something tells me: 3 girls 3 live tv, 1977, Piano, violin, percussion and vocal parts laid in. (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Holloway, Stanley see Martin Show, Tony
  - Honey & Sis
    - Boogie nights (Box-folder 13/17)
    - La Cucaracha (Box-folder 13/18)
    - The disco of life Life is a disco tag (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Happy hour (Box-folder 13/20)
    - One act’s enough, Composed and arranged by Chris Boardman. (Box-folder 13/21)
    - Razz ma tazz me (Box-folder 13/22)
    - Slipped disco (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Theatre B Theatre E (Box-folder 13/24)
    - [Three] 3 is a crowd (Box-folder 13/25)
    - You’re a grand old flag (Box-folder 13/26)
  - Hope, Bob
    - Get ready: t.v., Arranged by J. Hill. (Box-folder 13/27)
    - The way we were, For Hope and Lucille Ball. (Box-folder 13/28)
  - Hopkins, Mary
    - There’s no business like show business: Nov. 17, 1969 (Box-folder 13/29)
  - Horne, Lena see also American Express
    - Just a little lovin’: July 9, 1968 (Box-folder 13/30)
    - Love me tonight: July 8, 1969 (Box-folder 13/31)
  - Hustle my bustle (Box-folder 13/32)
  - I do what I please: M-103 (end credits), Originally from Miscellaneous cues [envelope 2]. (Box-folder 13/33)
  - I won’t dance: strings and insert (Box-folder 13/34)
  - Jeffersons: film t.v. TAT, 1979
    - Jefferson’s rock, Originally from Miscellaneous cues [envelope 3]; composed by Byers. (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Jeffries, Fran
    - I [write] sing the songs: vaudeville 1977, Found in envelope of Anthony Newley arrangements. (Box-folder 14/2)
    - If I lose this dream (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Isn’t she lovely - sunshine medley: vaudeville 1977, Includes: "You are the sunshine of my life." (Box-folder 14/4)
    - You are so beautiful [to me]: vaudeville 77 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Jones, Shirley
    - If I loved you (Box-folder 14/6)
    - Music Man medley, Includes: "Iowa stubborn;" "Goodnight, my someone;" "Pick-a-little, talk-a-little;" "Till there was you;" "Seventy-six trombones." (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Jones, Shirley and Jack Cassidy
    - Hello young lovers - opening (Box-folder 14/8)
    - Love love song (Box-folder 14/9)
    - Oklahoma medley, Includes: "Oklahoma!;" "Oh, what a beautiful morning;" "The surrey with the fringe on top;" "People will say we’re in love." (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Jones, Tom
    - Consider yourself (optional start): special, Jan. 10, 1972 Consider yourself dance end + vocal tag: special (Box-folder 14/11)
    - I’ll never fall in love again - reed replacements: Music Scene ABC-TV (Box-folder 14/12)
    - London bridge special/#1 opening London bridge special #13 - 14 - 15/ballet part V London bridge special #20 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Something - Hound dog - Whatever Lola wants: special, Jan. 8, 1972, For Hermione + Chief. (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Josh and Kelley
    - Josh and Kelley (Box-folder 14/15)
  - Jumps, Sonny see The Music Scene
  - June is busting out all over (Box-folder 14/16)
  - Keel, Howard and [Kathryn] Grayson
    - Make believe (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Keigo Imperial Dancers
    - Bugaboo babies: Jan. 1, 1967, Composed by Billy Byers. (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Closing soliloquy (Box-folder 14/19)
  - Kelly, Gene see also Hamill, Dorothy
    - Our love is here to stay: Dorothy Hamill tv special1976 (Box-folder 14/20)
  - Kim, Primo and the Wild Affairs
    - After today: Aug. 16, 1969 After today’s bows (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Eleanor Rigby: Aug. 18, 1969 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - I’ll remember you: Aug. 16, 1969 I’ll remember you fix (Box-folder 14/23)
    - It’s wild: Aug. 18, 1969, Composed by Primo Kim. (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Mission - rock - bullwhip (Box-folder 14/25)
    - The music that makes me dance (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Walking happy: July 11, 1969 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Where am I going (Box-folder 14/28)
    - The windmills of your mind: Aug. 18, 1969 (Box-folder 14/29)
  - King, B. B.
    - All I want: The Music Scene ABC-TV (Box-folder 15/1)
    - The thrill is gone: The Music Scene ABC-TV, Nov. 6, 1969 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Ladd, Cheryl
    - Credits: special, 1979 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Dear Aunt Caroline: special, 1979 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Got to get you into my life (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Missing you: tv special, 1979 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - To make you smile again: tv special, 1979 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Lambert, Hugh
    - Baltimore (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Puttin’ on the ritz: Jan. 29, 1972 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Lambert, Hugh and Nancy Sinatra
    - Slap that bass: Jan. 15, 1972 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Lamour, Dorothy
    - South Sea medley, Includes: "Moonlight and shadows;" "Sunday, Monday or always;" "But beautiful;" "I remember you;" "Moonlight becomes you;" "It could happen to you;" "Personality." (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Lane, Abbe